[Music]
The leaf is turning, but what colour will
it be?
Look closer, change is the very nature of
being.
From a moment to a memory, drenched
clothes to fur coats,
a shack to a skyscraper, radical to a
plant,
the universe has come a long way.
There will be a few misses with
approaching patchy shadows,
but will surely be followed by a clear
sky.
Let us join hands to replace patterns,
to create, witness and approach a new
goal.
Let us shatter the shroud of the leaves.
Petals fade, but let not our minds and
hearts.
Slap your wings with the flowing change.
Allow change for the unknown, the unborn
and the alchemy.
Accept change as we are no slaves to time
and mind.
Embrace change as we are all about man's
attempt at false stability.
Shuffle and reshuffle to unravel
positivity
and to make us love and live more.
Let us all unite to accelerate the
paradigm shift.
[Music]